

NGUYEN VAN A

MARKETING MANAGER

Male

May 19, 1992

♥ Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and shoreditch direct trade four dollar toast copper mug." Co of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

EDUCATION



FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. or randomised words which don't look even administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

EXPERIENCE



Sep 2007 - Present

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult dich and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to with a man who chooses to enjoy a pleasure that has no annoying conseque goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

ACTIVITIES





Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer slation by Harris Rackham reads:
- "Nor is there anyone who lov' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

CERTIFICATIONS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO

2013 - 2014

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US ngoại ngữ khác không? Hãy gửi e-mail cho chúng tôi với cá

REFERENCES



NGUYEN VAN BINH

director of cvpro jsc

U 01234567890 mbinhnv@topcv.com

SKILLS



Words Photoshop Excel **English** Power Point • **Japanese**

INTERESTS



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt he 15th century who is thought to have scrambled parts of Cicero's De and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities